Who's that?
MURDER IN THE NIGHTLIFE DISTRICT II
- That's Park Hyeon-jun.
- Park Hyeon-jun?
WHY IS PARK HYEON-JUN
IN A PHOTO LEE GUN-JUN HAD?
- Hang on.
- The boy's name is Park Hyeon-jun.
PARK HYEON-JUN
- Park Hyeon-jun?
- I thought he was Lee Gun-jun.
- That's odd.
- Is Gun-jun actually Hyeon-jun?
It doesn't make any sense.
So here's the deal.
I only realized it myself
during the briefing.
- Mr. Attorney.
- Yes?
- You were texting with a guy
- by the name of Park Hyeon-jun.
- That's right.
However, Lee Gun-mi had the same
string of texts on her phone.
I knew she wasn't who she claimed to be,
but I never imagined
she'd have a third name.
- Who was the Park Hyeon-jun you met?
- What are you on about?
- I--
- What did he look like?
You'd know since you were in bed with him.
- But Park Hyeon-jun's a guy.
- Yes, a guy.
- Wasn't that Lee Gun-jun's alias?
- Wasn't he also Lee Gun-jun?
I don't know Lee Gun-jun.
Why'd he keep Hyeon-jun's family photo
if he wasn't Hyeon-jun himself?
- Exactly, which is why it's odd.
- Right.
Hear me out.
Check out Park Hyeon-jun in the photo.
- The nostrils are heart-shaped.
- Heart-shaped nostrils.
The Park Hyeon-jun in this photo
also has heart-shaped nostrils.
Are you the nostril evaluator?
Here's a photo of Lee Gun-jun,
but you can't tell
the shape of his nostrils.
- Let's go.
- Let's check the victim's body.
- Check the victim's nostrils.
- If they're heart-shaped,
- the victim is Hyeon-jun.
- Gun-mi.
How can Gun-mi
not have heart-shaped nostrils?
- I never had a reason to check.
- All right, let's see.
- They're heart-shaped!
- They're heart-shaped.
- Are you sure?
- They're heart-shaped for sure.
- Gun-mi, Gun-jun, and Park Hyeon-jun.
- They all have heart-shaped nostrils.
They're the same person.
Why did he go by Lee Gun-jun
in high school, then?
- Beats me.
- Even his dad's surname is Park.
- How do you know the officer?
- Yeah, and why did you take this photo?
How do you know Park Lieutenant?
As I mentioned,
we were colleagues a long time ago.
- Why did you steal the photo?
- Why did you take it?
Because to me, she was a fraud.
Then she suddenly showed up at my club,
and I found out she had
a photo of my former colleague.
Park Hyeon-jun, Lee Gun-jun,
and Lee Gun-mi were the same person.
So what does that indicate?
The one who has ties to Kim Club's past
is the dead Lee Gun-mi.
I'm sure Club is somehow connected
to Lee Gun-jun's father.
What about this brick?
There's clearly blood on it.
That can only mean
the culprit used it to strike the victim.
- That's right.
- No.
- The brick isn't the murder weapon.
- They did.
- No? Why not?
- No.
I'll come clean.
- That one's on me.
- What?
That's what I used
to beat the crap out of Gu Ninety.
- I used it.
- Seriously, lady.
- Are you kidding me?
- I knew it.
- Seriously!
- Look, the corner or the side of the brick
- couldn't have made that gash.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, the shape doesn't match.
I threw that around
while beating up Gu Ninety.
What is it?
Did the chicken lady do something?
- Dancer.
- Yes?
Give me your purse.
- Tell me what she did first.
- I'll take care of that.
- What?
- I want to know what she did.
She beat up Gu Ninety with that brick.
SEARCHING AN DANCER'S PURSE
Is this where you store
the footage you filmed?
I don't know.
- Detective, here you go.
- What is it?
- What's that?
- Who knows?
- Let's check what's on this.
- Where can we do that?
I'm sure the footage on this
will show how this guy
is connected to all of this.
There's a folder titled "VIP."
I hope my photos aren't there.
"Gae Politician Marijuana."
-"Na Star Ecstasy."
-"Wang Chaebol."
-"Wang Chaebol Meth"?
Unbelievable.
- He must be Na Star. Unbelievable.
- Oh dear.
- They're having a blast.
- I had no idea.
- Seriously?
- Oh dear.
Look how buff Chaebol is.
This is outrageous.
She's out to ruin my club.
How can this be her fault
when you're the one hosting these parties?
I never gave her permission
to take photos.
You really dodged a bullet here.
I'd never let myself
be compromised this way.
-"An Dancer"?
INFORMANT - AN DANCER
That's a good shot.
Her plastic surgery
was more than just a success.
Can 500 million
really buy you a face like this?
- Informant? There's more?
- Informant? "Informant Profile."
Is An Dancer the informant?
- Who was her handler?
- Who did she work for?
Lee Gun-mi?
Hey, Dancer!
- Yes?
- Get over here.
- Me?
- Hey.
I'll punch you once
for every second that passes.
- What is it?
- Who were you passing information to?
- What?
- Who did you work for?
What do you mean?
This isn't your flash drive, is it?
If it were, it wouldn't have files
calling you the informant.
Spill it. Where did you steal it from?
The flash drive...
That's not mine. I found it.
- You found it?
- Where, exactly?
- Please, not your right fist.
- Save it for later.
- Give me some time.
- Give me time to explain.
- Save it for the culprit.
She's going to talk.
Where did you find it?
It was Gun-mi's.
I knew it.
- Did you beat her to death and take it?
- Did you steal it then?
I was at Hansim Pocha for the meeting
when Mr. Club told me
to check the water leak detector.
Do you remember that?
- You sent me out twice.
- I sent you out twice.
- Why did you send her to check on it?
- What time was that?
Because the water leak detector
was malfunctioning.
- It's the one at our club.
- We're in a flood-prone district,
and my club is below ground.
There's always water damage,
so I installed a water leak detector.
He sent me out twice that night
because the detector went off again.
I left Hansim Pocha around 10:40 p.m.
and made my way to the club.
I gave Gun-mi that flash drive
after putting the photos on it,
so I knew what it looked like.
When I saw a flash drive
identical to that on the ground,
I got curious and picked it up.
- Was that this flash drive?
- That was it.
I hear you, so continue talking over here.
- By the body's feet.
- Why?
I just want to do a camera test.
- Right here. Do we have the visual?
- I bet this is something weird.
- It's not.
- Of course not.
We're checking if you still look good
- on the thermal camera.
- Did you hear me? I just found it.
- We hear you.
- We do.
- Gold Spoon.
- She looks good.
I knew I could count on you
to listen to me.
Even with this, you can tell people apart.
If we check the recordings,
we'll find out who was here.
IDENTIFIABLE TO SOME DEGREE
Dancer, didn't I tell you
to practice your dancing?
How can a dancer be so bad at dancing?
Unbelievable.
Is there recorded footage or anything?
Just a second.
Wouldn't it be
on the camera's memory card?
THIS CAMERA MIGHT'VE CAUGHT SOMETHING
- Let's check this out.
- Here we go.
Did you find it?
RECORDED FOOTAGE
FROM THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT
- What is it?
- You found it?
- It's playing.
- It was at 9:15 p.m.
- No way.
- Hold on.
- Her hair!
- Oh my gosh.
- No way.
- Hold on.
- Her hair!
- Oh my gosh.
- That's me. Sorry, guys.
- That's you, Ms. Chicken.
- That's clearly you.
- Look.
- It's her.
- I don't hit her though. Keep looking!
Wait, who's the other person?
- Gun-mi, of course.
- It's Gun-mi.
Is this before or after
you beat up Gu Ninety?
After. This was at 9:15 p.m.
- She dragged the victim out by her hair.
- She dragged her out.
I may have pulled her by the hair,
but I didn't kill her.
- And?
- I took her purse.
- Why did you take it?
- Why?
I saw she had a passport,
so I told her not to mess up
if she wanted it back.
But she had her passport with her.
- I gave it back to her.
- When?
- That means you saw her again.
- Well, yeah.
Hey, it's rude to point at your elders.
A SWIFT CHANGE IN DIRECTION
It's just...
Anyway, I beat the crap out of a man
thinking he was Lee Eighty,
so wouldn't I be pissed to find out
he was Gu Ninety?
- That's understandable.
- I had to pay 20 million won to settle.
- Of course, I was fuming.
- Sure.
Didn't Gun-mi deserve to die?
- She did.
When I got back,
I saw her outside her house.
- So I dragged her to the empty lot.
- Here?
I threatened to kill her,
and she begged me not to.
At that point, I was sure she was a woman.
- I couldn't beat up a petite girl.
- Of course, you couldn't.
I was so pissed off
that I kicked the big metal sheet.
- Hold on. When was this?
- It says so right here. 9:15 p.m.
Of course!
I actually heard a loud crashing sound.
- I heard the clanking at 9:15 p.m. too!
- Was it the sound of her kicking this?
- Oh, that's what that sound was?
- Sorry about that.
For a moment,
I thought it was an earthquake.
- I assumed it was construction.
- Just how strong is this lady?
Her kicks are as good as her punches.
I threatened to take her passport
if she didn't bring me Lee Eighty.
I told her to bring him,
and she said
to meet her somewhere at 9:30 p.m.
And at 9:35 p.m., I actually met the guy.
I'm pretty sure I spent an hour
beating him to a pulp.
- And?
- Until 10:35 p.m.?
We should be looking
for Lee Eighty's body.
- There will be a second body.
- Maybe he's buried here.
- So, did Lee Eighty die?
- Anyway...
Where's Lee Eighty?
Who knows? Maybe he bolted.
Didn't you say
you last saw her at 9:15 p.m.?
I never said it was when I saw her last.
That's suspicious.
When you line up our alibis,
the last person who saw the victim
is Ha Gold Spoon at 9:45 p.m.
That's what he said.
We need to keep digging.
I wonder what they did after meeting up.
Ha Gold Spoon, that little brat.
I was being nice because he's my landlord,
and now he's acting all arrogant.
SEARCHING GOLD SPOON'S COMPUTER
What has he been up to?
Look at this.
C-store's father-in-law chewed him out.
- He asked what C-store has been up to.
- That was sent at 9:30 p.m.
- Mr. Attorney!
- But...
Yes?
- Where are you?
- I'm over here.
Could you come here?
I found something suspicious
on your computer.
Why do you have a shortcut to Darkscene?
Darkscene?
- Darkscene. The name itself is shady.
- That sounds familiar.
ENTER EMAIL AND PASSWORD
- Even Gun-mi had an account.
-"Gunmi"?
-"Goldspoon" and "Gunmi."
-"Goldspoon," huh?
- Give us the password.
- What now?
Which password will you give us first?
Gun-mi's or Gold Spoon's?
What's Gun-mi's password?
- Why does her name pop up?
- She logged on from here.
Why does it show she logged on from here?
"Gunmi"?
I don't know about Gun-mi's,
but Goldspoon is my account.
- What's the password? Or just type it in.
- Give us the password.
Figure it out yourselves.
- As if that's possible.
- The clue's "heart."
- Heart?
- Heart.
- How do you type that in?
- H, E, A, R, T.
- Mr. Kim, how can you not know that?
Sorry.
I thought he meant
the heart symbol, Dancer.
What about "heart nose"?
- Heart nostrils?
- Heart nostrils.
It can't be.
- Maybe it's a numeric code. "Heart."
- Did he not write it down somewhere?
It's normal to write down
a complicated password.
I know what he meant by "heart."
- What is it?
- Here.
Type S and the number two side by side,
and you get a heart.
Try "S2S2."
-"S2S2."
- The number two?
- Yeah, the number two.
-"S2S2." That has to be it.
LOGIN SUCCESSFUL
Nice one, Dancer!
- I'm giving you a 50,000-won raise.
- Thank you.
What do we have here?
-"Jang Candidate's Illegal Funding."
- Call him Ha Psycho.
"Hammer Construction Bid Rigging."
-"Park Hyeon-jun Retribution Video."
What the heck?
PARK HYEON-JUN RETRIBUTION VIDEO
Oh dear.
- He has a bob.
- Chestnut Makgeolli sounds familiar.
Right?
Did you see that?
I taught Park Hyeon-jun a lesson.
What do you think? Aren't you satisfied?
Gold Spoon,
this is Park Hyeon-jun's phone.
I'll make sure to delete
the photo and the texts.
Wait, I remember seeing
that sky-blue blouse somewhere.
The blouse that was cut down the middle.
Isn't it the blouse that was cut in half?
Hold on. Why is this blouse cut up?
FOUND AT LEE GUN-JUN'S HOUSE
IS IT THE SAME BLOUSE FROM THE VIDEO?
I deleted the photo.
Now, I'll delete the texts.
All gone.
Mission complete.
- Hang on.
- Who's the guy in the video?
- Isn't that the victim doing all that?
- That's it.
- It was a one-man show.
- Exactly.
- He put on a show.
- He wore half of that blouse.
- Park Hyeon-jun is the one talking.
- He wore the blouse
and filmed a video of himself
looking all battered.
- This is how he did it.
- Exactly.
This is Park Hyeon-jun.
The camera's in selfie mode,
and he's faking the pain.
- And then...
- Did you see that?
- He switched hands.
- I taught Park Hyeon-jun a lesson.
He's saying that line as Gun-mi.
Yeah, only one hand
is visible at all times.
Mission complete.
- Is there a reflection?
- We're right.
It was a one-man show.
She played you good, Gold Spoon.
- You must've been furious.
- Let me explain.
- Go ahead.
- She got you good.
I met Lee Gun-mi at Sensibility Bar.
She agreed to go out,
but suddenly claimed she was busy
and said she couldn't meet up.
Honestly, it pissed me off.
I was wondering what to do
when I saw someone
who was totally my type
outside the convenience store.
- I ran into Park Hyeon-jun.
- The guy with heart-shaped nostrils.
Heart-nose. You met a heart-nose.
I wasn't getting anywhere with Lee Gun-mi,
so Hyeon-jun and I went out
for a glass of whiskey.
But I totally blacked out.
I'm guessing it was the same drug.
Like that time
when I couldn't remember anything, huh?
After I woke up,
he asked about our night
and said he had a good time.
He said he enjoyed it,
so I took it as a positive sign
and we parted ways.
But then, I got a text.
You saw it earlier.
- It was the photo of us in bed together.
- Yes.
I always have them sign a contract
before taking it further.
Was this signed the day you two hooked up?
He signed it,
but then took it from me.
I said I'd pay 50 million won
if he deleted the photo.
After he got the money,
he deleted the photo,
and everything was fine again.
- But then Gun-mi suddenly reached out.
- Okay.
I wanted to be with her
since she'll forever be
the woman of my dreams.
- He just won't stop.
- We agreed to go out,
but she came to my office instead.
That's probably when you saw her.
- That's probably it.
- That's when Dancer saw her.
Out of the blue, she went, "So?"
"Are you gay?"
She then showed me a text she received.
- And?
- It was that photo.
I thought Park Hyeon-jun had deleted it,
but he somehow sent a copy to Gun-mi.
- Gun-mi put on one heck of a show.
- You got swindled by both sides.
Once by Park Hyeon-jun
and once by Lee Gun-mi.
- I didn't know.
- Oh boy.
Anyway, she said she knew a place
that handled this kind of business.
So I asked her to handle it,
and she sent me that video on August 11th.
How much did you pay?
- Did you get ripped off again?
- How much was this video worth?
- I'm guessing a 9-figure sum.
- How much was it?
- 200 million?
200 million won?
Park Hyeon-jun
scammed you out of 50 million won,
and then Lee Gun-mi
scammed you out of 200 million won.
You were scammed out of 250 million
by the same person.
Oh dear.
- You must've wanted to kill her.
- Exactly.
I paid him five million won first,
so he ended up taking
255 million won from me.
Mr. Gold Spoon may be an attorney
who acts all smart,
but he was scammed twice.
His political career hit a roadblock,
his father disapproved of him,
and he lost more than 200 million won.
But that wasn't the end.
There was a good chance
he'd get blackmailed again.
If he had realized the video
was a one-man show,
I don't think Ha Gold Spoon
would've just let it go.
Here's what I want to know.
What's with this photo?
Is that C-store's phone?
- Yeah, C-store's.
- C-store?
"You have one scary son-in-law."
What were you doing?
You were wearing a similar mask
when you were first brought in.
Anyway, this came
to his father-in-law's attention.
And he said, "What is this?
What have you been doing?"
I bet you were practicing
to copy those random assaults.
- What was this?
- Maybe he committed those assaults!
It wasn't me!
- With that face,
- How do we trust you?
- he could pass for any age group.
- You bet.
This must be the gift Lee Gun-mi sent.
- Oh, you're right.
-"Hope you're ready."
- Gun-mi must've spied on him
and sent the photos to his father-in-law.
- Knowing he was planning another assault...
- Hence, "You have one scary son-in-law."
C-store, are you the one
behind the random assaults?
You just came up with a story yourselves.
Speak while I'm still being nice.
My father-in-law sent me those messages
and then flew into a rage.
He chewed me out on the phone
for 15 minutes.
So I ignored his calls after that.
Tell us why you were wearing that mask.
And what's that in your hand?
Is that a claw hammer?
- What?
- It brings me peace, that's all.
- What do you mean? Wearing a mask?
- Wearing a mask?
Yeah.
When I wear a mask and hold a hammer...
- Yeah?
- That makes me feel at ease.
Looking at a particular body part...
- also puts me at ease.
- Exactly.
- What's with him?
- I found your fetish odd,
but I felt a connection earlier.
- Hey, give me your bag.
- Wait.
SEARCHING HIS BAG
This is gross.
Just so you know,
you can wear this both ways.
He was wearing a black mask
when he first arrived at the scene,
but he was wearing a red one in the photo.
You can wear it both ways, inside and out.
I switch it up depending on my mood.
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
- I go around wearing that.
- Do you roam the streets?
- Is that part of your routine?
- Did you use your weapon or not?
Have you assaulted anyone?
I swear,
never in this neighborhood.
Not in this neighborhood?
Oh jeez.
But that has absolutely nothing to do
with the case at hand.
That's for us to figure out.
Wouldn't there be information
on Gun-mi's account, Detective?
- Why did she log on from here?
- What's her password?
We should check Gun-mi's place as well.
I want to check Gun-jun's belongings.
- Okay, then let's all go there.
- I want to look into Mr. Club.
Mr. Kim Club.
- Yes?
- Where's your phone?
It's right here.
All right.
KIM CLUB'S PHONE
TEXTS ON KIM CLUB'S PHONE
The water leak detector.
WATER LEAK DETECTION SYSTEM
Hold on.
Mr. Club, who's Lieutenant Gu Lackey?
Lieutenant Gu Lackey?
A police officer, of course.
Gu Lackey texted,
"Sir, I looked into what you asked
but found nothing."
TEXT RECEIVED AT 9:55 P.M.
CALL MADE AT 10:05 P.M.
"Call me as soon as you get something."
What did you two talk about at 10:50 p.m.?
I asked him for a favor.
- A favor?
- Yeah.
I wonder what that was about.
MEANWHILE, AN DANCER IS SEARCHING
GANGSTER WHOLE CHICKEN
What the heck?
No way. It's a recording device.
Look here, chicken lady.
- What's this? Explain this.
- What?
What do you mean?
Hold on.
Tell me the story again
and be more specific.
This was all that skank Gun-mi's doing.
"This was all that skank Gun-mi's doing."
That must be Lee Eighty.
Lee Gun-mi first came up with the idea
to mess with your arm.
- Lee Gun-mi was behind it?
- Lee Gun-mi planned
and executed the whole thing.
Lee Gun-mi first came up with the idea
to mess with your arm.
Lee Gun-mi planned
and executed the whole thing.
Where's Lee Gun-mi now?
You're too late.
She probably already took off
with the money from the deal
after selling me out to you.
She probably took off
while you were beating the crap out of me
like a fool.
Based on what we just heard,
you realized Lee Gun-mi had played you.
That's right.
You beat up Gu Ninety
and Lee Eighty.
What did you do to Lee Gun-mi?
I went to get her.
Where?
To the airport.
I got in a taxi at 10:20 p.m.
But the roads were blocked,
so the taxi couldn't budge.
Even if I had made it to the airport,
it would've been too late to catch her
before her 11:59 p.m. flight.
So I gave up and came back.
That was around 11:10 p.m.
Is that it?
I had no contact with Gun-mi after that.
She had been beating up Lee Eighty
for about an hour.
That's how furious she was.
So, would she have given up
because of a traffic jam?
She had been hell-bent
on finding Lee Eighty,
who had ruined
her boxing career and dream.
But then she found out
Lee Eighty wasn't responsible.
Every path in this story
leads back to Lee Gun-mi.
ADDITIONAL SEARCH
OF FRAUD LEE GUN-MI'S HOUSE
CURRENTLY OFFLINE
Why doesn't the Wi-Fi work in his place?
The electricity's been cut off,
so there's no Wi-Fi there.
HE HEADS OUT TO FIND WI-FI
- What are you looking for?
- The Wi-Fi password.
The Wi-Fi?
- I remember seeing it.
- It's here.
- What's the password?
- The ID is "hansim,"
and the password is "1heart4car."
- What does this mean?
- Did you say "1heart4car"?
The password is "1heart4car."
Okay, "1heart4car."
CHECKING NETWORK REQUIREMENTS
I'm in. Nice, I got it.
The password translates to Hansim Pocha.
- Here's Gun-mi's account.
- Oh, look.
The password's been saved,
so you can log in.
Is that also Darkscene?
LEE GUN-MI'S ACCOUNT ON DARKSCENE
"I'll forward the photos
of the VIP drug parties."
"If things go south,
we can pin it all on her."
- She must be talking about Dancer!
- Oh dear. You saw this, didn't you?
- I haven't.
- I bet you saw it.
- I didn't.
- Don't lie.
- The house didn't have Wi-Fi.
- That's why it was inaccessible.
Gun-mi wrote the message
but died before she could send it.
The message was never sent.
- Even then, she could've seen it.
- But Dancer could've seen it.
If she did...
- I swear I never saw it.
- Sure, of course.
- High five.
- Are you sure?
- She saw it.
- She did.
- If you did, then you're the killer.
- Wait.
Did you check the contents
of the flash drive you found earlier?
Of course.
- You were on it as an informant.
- Yet, you didn't confront her?
Of course, I confronted her.
- What did you do?
- So?
- First of all...
- Hurry up and talk.
- It'll be a punch for every ten seconds.
- Okay, I'll talk.
After submitting the registration form
for the meeting at 9:15 p.m.,
I glanced out the office window
when I heard a loud crash.
Ms. Chicken and Gun-mi were fighting,
and I was wondering
whether I should step in or not.
- If you had, you'd be dead by now.
- Ms. Chicken left around 9:20 p.m.
So I called Gun-mi
and asked if she was all right.
She said she couldn't get the money
because of her
and asked to meet half an hour later.
So we agreed to meet at 9:50 p.m.
I attended the meeting
but stepped out briefly at 9:50 p.m.
- We ran into each other, remember?
- I do.
I saw her stepping out.
I was about to say hi,
- but she walked off without noticing me.
- That reminds me.
The water leak detector alarm went off,
so I was going to have her go check it.
But she had disappeared.
We had agreed
to meet outside Slam at 9:50 p.m.
I called her on my way there at 9:51 p.m.,
but her phone was turned off.
Something felt wrong,
so I headed to her place.
I went to her place,
but I swear I didn't see Darkscene.
All I saw was her plane ticket to Russia.
- The e-ticket?
- Yes.
It was odd because we had agreed
to flee to China together.
But she had already packed her suitcase
and booked a flight to Russia.
Anyway, you knew Lee Gun-mi
was planning to flee the country.
I found out at that moment.
I found out
that she was going to go to Russia,
but at that point, I still had no idea
what was on the flash drive.
I came across the flash drive
the second time Mr. Club sent me out,
and I checked it in the break room
at the club.
Once I learned her plan to flee to Russia
after handing my information over,
I called her at 10:55 p.m.
Even after five years
of paying off her debt,
An Dancer still had to work
another 50 years to clear it.
She thought she could pay off her debt
and debut in China,
so she must've been full of hope.
If she had read the text about pinning
the blame on her if things went south,
she would've realized Gun-mi was a fraud
and that she had been backstabbed.
She had been there for Gun-mi
and considered her a close friend,
but she was being used
for her to make money.
She would've been furious.
The thing that bothers me
is that Gun-jun's place had no Wi-Fi.
Given the urgency of the message,
he would've gone somewhere that had Wi-Fi.
According to the login records
we saw at Gold Spoon's office,
Gun-mi logged into her account
while she was there.
But I wonder why
the message didn't go through.
Did something happen
just as she was about to send it?
Here's what I think is important.
Whatever Gun-mi or Gun-jun did,
several people had to find one of the two.
There are two theories.
Some people can't have the victim,
Gun-jun, skip town.
They either have to make him pay
or get something from him.
The other theory
is related to Gun-jun's own plan.
He talked about revenge,
and we have to figure out
what that's about.
This man clearly
hasn't told us everything.
I'm sure there's more to it.
He needs to tell us
how he knows Park Hyeon-jun's father.
Let's listen to
what was on the recording device again.
How do you get this to play?
Come on, mister.
You try it, C-store.
- Devices these days are so complicated.
- I doubt he'll be any better.
- C-store can't seem to do it.
- Mister.
For any device to work...
(PRESSING THE BUTTON)
...you need to turn it on first.
- Wait, you hit the record button.
- How clever of you.
- The red one isn't the power button.
- Hey!
- It's the record button!
- Did you delete what was on it?
Hold on.
- Give me that.
- Come on, C-store.
I have somewhere to be,
so I'll be off now.
Wait, that was clearly intentional.
(PLAYING WHAT WAS JUST RECORDED)
- You recorded us instead!
- That's a recording of us!
FIRST-EVER EVIDENCE DESTRUCTION
ON CRIME SCENE
- Seriously, C-store.
- Hey, C-store.
Sorry about that.
I'll just say I'm the killer today.
Assume push-up position.
Let's spread out and keep looking!
We'll gather
after collecting more evidence!
SENSIBILITY BAR
There's a CCTV up here.
CCTV FILMING OUTSIDE SENSIBILITY BAR
JANG C-STORE SEARCHES THE POLICE STATION
This computer was being repaired earlier.
- They must've fixed it.
- It must be fixed now.
Everything's breaking down here
- because of the heavy rain.
- Tell me about it.
"Database."
"Find missing."
-"Search for missing child"?
- What?
- Jeez, where is this case going?
- My heart just sank.
Year of birth.
She was born in 1993, like me.
(SOMEONE ALREADY DID A SEARCH?)
"Maniac Province."
SEARCH
AN TWO YEARS, MALE, 1993
OH KIDS, MALE, 1993
- Who's that?
- We have it!
-"An Two Years."
- Here he is.
- Hang on.
- That's him.
- He has heart-shaped nostrils.
- Heart-shaped nostrils!
IS THIS LEE GUN-JUN, AKA PARK HYEON-JUN?
- Wait, these are missing children.
- Why was he missing?
When did he go missing?
- He was reported missing in 2002.
- He went missing in 2002.
Maybe this is a case of identity theft.
RESEARCHING LEE GUN-JUN'S HOUSE
Hold on.
- Why's this case so complicated?
- No way!
No way!
What now?
What is it?
I found out
why he went by a different name.
This is a surname and given name
registration application
filed by Care Orphanage.
The application concerns Lee Gun-jun,
an abandoned male child,
born January 1, 1993.
It says here, "I hereby authorize
the name of this abandoned child
as Lee Gun-jun."
"He wasn't able to verify his own name
or any information about his parents
when he was found."
This was in 2002.
In 2002, he legally became Lee Gun-jun.
After that, he started carrying two IDs,
one as Gun-jun and the other as Gun-mi,
once he reached adulthood.
What is all this about?
Mister, what did you do
to Park Hyeon-jun's father?
What happened in 2002?
Hey, mister.
I've got no issue
roughing up 57-year-olds.
There was an unfortunate incident.
- What, exactly?
- I can't believe him.
If I were 30 years older,
I would've beaten him up.
Let's find out for ourselves.
- Let's figure it out.
- Get searching.
- Hey, let's go.
- Figure it out and then come back to me.
- Go to the club.
- Let's head to the club.
- You won't be able to find anything.
- Head to the club.
Wait, C-store.
Didn't you say you wanted to
listen to some music?
Yeah.
Let me play it for you.
HIS FRIEND IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO CARES ABOUT HIM...
ARE YOU READY?
What did you press?
FASCINATED
THANKS TO HIS FRIEND, HE ENJOYS
HIS FIRST CLUBBING EXPERIENCE
This is what we do around here.
I love it.
PARTY TIME
EXHILARATING
Hey, hold on.
Is that the best you can dance?
Does the hand need to go up to the ear?
Yeah, like this.
C-store, are you enjoying
your first time at a club?
- I'm having a blast.
- C-store seemed curious.
WHILE JANG C-STORE ENJOYS HIMSELF
What could be there?
"You have one scary son-in-law"?
SEARCHING THE EMPTY CONVENIENCE STORE
These are the dolls.
UNDER THE REGISTER
A DOCUMENT ENVELOPE?
Detective.
REPORTING IT TO THE DETECTIVE
Check this out.
That little bastard.
That little bastard!
What's this?
- That's the water leak detector.
- The detector.
Because we're below ground,
it frequently malfunctions
and goes off spontaneously.
It malfunctioned twice today.
- You had it fixed, right?
- That little bastard!
- What did he say?
- Hey, you bastard!
Is he talking to C-store?
What now?
You punk, I ought to teach you a lesson.
- What is it?
- What now?
You piece of trash.
RANDOM ATTACK OCCURS AT NIGHT...
- You attacked someone with a hammer.
-"Swung a hammer." Why, you little...
"The assailant indiscriminately swung
a hammer at a passerby in an alley."
You bastard.
He said earlier he didn't attack anyone
in this neighborhood.
- Exactly, it was in the Seoul area.
- He did it in Gangjong District.
RANDOM ATTACK OCCURS AT NIGHT...
"How much do you think I know?"
As long as Lee Gun-jun got away alive,
he could report the crime anytime.
To avoid going to prison,
C-store had to kill him.
I didn't want to worry the people
in this neighborhood.
This is nuts.
That's why I went as far away as I could
to commit these crimes.
- I mean it.
- Are you serious?
I didn't attack anyone around here.
- Listen to the details of this article.
- Okay.
"The crime occurred on a rainy day,
targeting a woman
under 160 cm in height with long hair."
- Lee Gun-mi was short.
- That's true.
What if C-store didn't know
that Gun-jun was Gun-mi at the time?
I mean, Gun-mi clearly
looked like a woman.
Also, it rained last night, right?
- It did.
- Yes, it rained.
On a rainy day, the petite Lee Gun-mi
was dressed like a woman.
She was hit on the head with a hammer.
We all saw the wound.
Why should we assume he only attacked
people in other neighborhoods?
I had been suspicious of the wooden dolls
because they all had umbrellas
and long hair.
Something about them gave me the chills.
I think there's a good chance
C-store just thought she matched
the profile of the women he targets
for his random attacks and attacked her.
The woman he attacked
could've just turned out to be
none other than Lee Gun-jun.
There has to be more on Kim Club.
What could he have done to Park Hyeon-jun?
Where was that photo of Park Hyeon-jun?
- At Gun-mi's place.
- Let's go there.
WOULD THERE BE A CLUE
AT LEE GUN-JUN'S HOUSE?
He even packed his razor.
Gosh, I need a quick bite.
Can we stop by the convenience store?
Me too.
Hold on.
Who's this?
I've often been told that I look like her.
Come on, she's pretty.
You two look nothing alike.
I look just like her.
- Mr. Club, don't I look just like her?
- Who's she?
People say I look like her.
- She's stunning.
- No way. Unlike you, she's beautiful.
A fake can never look like the original.
- Your hair's not styled like hers.
- Give it up already.
(DANG IT)
I found something else.
Of course.
I knew it.
A PIECE OF PAPER WAS INSIDE AN ENVELOPE
ALONG WITH A POLICE ID?
What the heck?
What?
- Kim Club!
- Kim Club?
- Get over here.
- Come on, mister. I mean, Mr. Kim.
"Center News."
"A Policeman's Family of Four
Killed in Fire."
DRUG RING'S INVOLVEMENT SUSPECTED
"The victims are Park Lieutenant
of Seoul's Gangdam Police Station,
who received recognition last year
as an exemplary officer,
along with his wife, Ms. Kim,
and their 9-year-old son."
- Their son? Is that Park Hyeon-jun?
- Yeah, it is.
Look at him casually eating.
- He scares me.
- He scares me too.
This part has been crossed out
with a red pen.
"The police received a tip
that Park had been colluding
with a drug ring."
AT THE TIME, KIM CLUB WAS THE DIRTY COP
WORKING WITH THE DRUG RING
Kim Club framed Park Lieutenant.
DID HE MAKE PARK LIEUTENANT HIS FALL GUY...
How reprehensible.
...AND KILL HIS ENTIRE FAMILY?
You killed his entire family?
Gun-jun even had this.
- What's that?
- What else could it be?
It's your old police ID.
My eyesight is going in my old age.
So the victim's revenge
was definitely aimed at Kim Club.
That's why there was gasoline.
- Right here. This gasoline.
- To avenge the fire with fire.
But seeing that he went as far
as getting gasoline for his revenge,
he wouldn't have fled to Moscow
before seeing it through.
- Fair point.
- He'd never do that.
- That's why he stayed behind.
- Who knows?
Something urgent must've come up.
Or perhaps you killed him first.
He died before he could use the gasoline.
You said you came by the house.
Didn't you notice the gasoline
when you took the photo?
How could I have noticed that?
The photo completely threw me off.
I had only thought of her
as a weird little fraud,
so I couldn't understand
how she had that photo.
I just grabbed it in a hurry,
which is why it got ripped in the corner.
I couldn't shake off the suspicion
after seeing it,
so I took it to Gu Lackey,
who was at the police station,
to show him.
I asked him to look the girl up
in the missing children database
because I thought she might be alive.
He said he couldn't find anything,
but it kept bothering me.
So, I called Gu Lackey again.
AUGUST 12, 2020, WEDNESDAY
LIEUTENANT GU LACKEY, 10:05 P.M.
That's when I realized
her age didn't add up.
I'd assumed it was the little girl,
but maybe it was the boy.
So I asked him to check
on the missing boys instead.
And Gu Lackey got back to me
and told me that he got a hit.
- A boy?
- Yes, a boy.
So that's when you figured it out.
To achieve his goal,
he wiped out an entire family.
After seeing the family photo
at the victim's house,
he looked into the matter, just in case,
only to learn that a child survived,
and that it was none other than Gun-mi.
You can imagine
how anxious he must've felt.
Let's say he went to Gun-mi's house
while trembling in fear.
What if he spotted the gasoline?
Then that would've answered it.
His gut instinct would've told him
that the victim was seeking revenge.
Given that,
he could've thought of
killing the victim first.
Detective, we have
all the circumstantial evidence.
Everyone here
had a reason to kill the victim.
Dancer would've killed her
if she had seen the message.
Club would've wanted to stop her
since he was the target for revenge.
I also had a reason to kill her
since she ruined my life.
And as for him,
he was scammed out of 200 million won.
- That's chump change to me.
- He had more to lose than just his money.
I was simply worried
that she could jeopardize my future.
And as for this kid here,
he could've been the killer,
even if it was voluntary manslaughter.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- True.
- The perfect target for his random attacks
just happened to show up on a rainy day.
There's no doubt
a deep-seated grudge
fueled this vicious attack.
There was a struggle,
and marks on her body
suggest a violent altercation,
but the soles of her shoes were too clean.
Also, we still haven't found
the murder weapon.
In that case, there's a possibility
that the murder didn't take place
at the empty lot.
- All right.
- If she had been attacked elsewhere,
wouldn't there be bloodstains or a weapon
in another location?
Look, check this out.
Look at the scars on her back.
There are four streaks
running vertically.
These scratches couldn't have been made
by a human hand.
She was slammed
against an object with this pattern.
- She was pushed against something.
- In that case,
should we find the place
that might have something of that pattern?
- That's what we need to find.
- Yeah.
Let's scatter and look for
what could've made that mark.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
THAT MATCHES THE PATTERN
HANSIM POCHA
GANGDAM DISTRICT
LEASE DISPUTE CONSULTATION CENTER
KARAOKE
GANGDAM STATION YOUTH STREET MEETING
WITH BUSINESS OWNERS AFFECTED BY COVID-19
Jeez, this is a tough one.
- Hey, Dancer.
- Yes?
Does anything seem suspicious to you?
You, actually.
Over here! Could this have done it?
This AC condenser unit right here.
- The pattern's similar.
- Don't you think they match?
- This has a similar pattern.
- Right here.
- You're right.
- It looks similar.
- This has to be it.
- It's similar. Good work.
- Hold on.
- It's similar.
- Check this out.
- Well found.
- Let's say he was pushed into this.
- Yeah.
Wait, look!
There are some strands of hair here!
- He was slammed against the wall.
- That's how he got that gash.
His head was slammed against this wall!
HEAD WOUND
TORN-OFF FLESH AND HAIR
- There are strands of hair stuck here.
- I get it.
The rain washed away the bloodstains.
This is the alley
next to Ms. Chicken's restaurant.
- Yeah, it is.
- It is.
What's this?
Come on, Ms. Chicken.
- What's this area?
- Ms. Chicken.
What's that? That one right there!
- Isn't that blood?
- It's blood.
What on earth?
Ms. Chicken, you're busted.
You're not going to say
it's chicken blood, are you?
I know nothing about this.
Besides, anyone can come in here.
See? It's open to anyone.
Why is there blood on this box?
- It couldn't have been wiped on this.
- Beats me.
It doesn't look like blood spatter.
It could be chicken blood.
How should I know?
- Listen.
- How is this chicken blood?
I live my life covered in blood.
- Did Gun-mi invite you to Sensibility Bar?
- Hold on.
- She did, yeah.
- There's blood on this belt too.
- What?
- What's that?
- Is that the only bloodstain?
- Yeah.
- How...
- Are you sure it's blood?
- You can easily pop this out.
- Maybe she was hit with this.
- Detective, teach C-store a lesson.
- She was banged up.
The culprit battered the victim with this.
- All right, so this is the crime scene.
- This is where it happened.
- Right here.
- Hold on.
- But this... Hang on.
- This is what I think.
After she was thrust against the wall,
she was strangled against this.
Then she was beaten with this pole.
The killer grabbed this pole.
See how there's blood here?
- The victim had bruises all over.
- She was beaten up with that.
- The killer beat the crap out of her.
- Right.
I don't think
this was a premeditated crime.
- It was voluntary manslaughter.
- Exactly.
After killing someone like that,
you need to get rid of the body.
The recycling station was empty
at the time,
so the killer put her there first.
The killer briefly hid the body
at the recycling station,
but it was discovered in the empty lot.
So it means
the killer moved the body there.
But why did they move the body?
And since the body was moved...
We need to determine
how the body was moved.
Did the killer carry the body?
- If so...
- That means they're strong.
The body could've been carried.
It could've also been pushed
on a cart or something.
There are many possible scenarios.
So how was the body moved?
WHERE THE BODY WAS FOUND
WHERE THE MURDER TOOK PLACE
I bet there's something around here
that could've been used to move the body.
It'd be too exhausting to carry the body,
especially on a rainy day.
I'm sure there's something here.
NO ENTRY
DETOUR ADVISED DUE TO ROAD FLOOD
FLOOD RESTRICTION SIGN
Oh shit.
IT LIFTS UP?
Check this out.
- What?
- Where did you find that?
- What's that?
- Was that used to move the body?
With this?
This must be it.
- There's blood!
- Is there blood?
BLOODSTAINS?
- I didn't realize this had wheels.
- It does.
I looked for something with wheels,
and this was the only thing around.
THE CULPRIT MOVED THE BODY
WITH THE FLOOD RESTRICTION SIGN
This is what the culprit used for sure.
C-store, you scored a big one.
Even a woman could've easily
pushed this to the lot.
- The women remain as suspects.
- Anyone could've done it.
That being said, the body...
Which route did they take?
You had to either take the route
that passes the police station
or the one that goes past Sensibility Bar.
Going past the police station
wasn't an option,
which means the killer
pushed the body past the bar
while the truck was parked outside it.
Detective.
The delivery truck
- should've parked here.
- The delivery truck?
- Yeah
- Exactly.
But it couldn't park here
because the road was blocked.
- That was 10:10 p.m.
- Right.
- Hear me out.
- Sure.
- It parked here instead.
- Did it actually park here?
By doing so,
it blocked the view of this CCTV.
Because the truck blocked the CCTV...
- The entire road became a blind spot.
- Exactly.
So, after killing Lee Gun-mi,
someone had the chance
to secretly dump the body
by getting past this blind spot.
I'm sure we can access the footage
from this CCTV.
MUST CHECK THE CCTV FOOTAGE
SENSIBILITY BAR
What is it?
What now?
- That was unexpected.
- What is it?
ANOTHER DOOR?
I knew it.
No wonder.
Sneaky bastards.
It opens.
A DOOR LEADING INSIDE SENSIBILITY BAR
Sneaky bastards.
IS BEING PRETTY A CRIME?
Being sneaky, huh?
Oh, here's the footage.
You can check the footage here.
Oh, it's the road outside the front door.
What the heck? Jeez, it's Gold Spoon.
- How do you work this?
- It's in real-time.
Let's check from 10:10 p.m.
CCTV RECORDING
- What time is it?
- The truck's approaching!
- What's with that truck?
- That's it.
There's the truck.
- What time was that?
- It says 10:15 p.m.
Yes, it was around 10:10 p.m.
It completely blocked the view.
We might see the killer
through that small gap.
The taillights went out.
The engine was turned off.
- There's more.
- Right.
- Are there multiple videos?
- Yeah.
This was at 10:29 p.m.
- Right, 10:29 p.m.
- Yeah.
- The truck should be leaving now.
- It's leaving.
- The truck's leaving.
- That was at 10:30 p.m.
- Well, well.
- It was exactly 15 minutes.
Someone would've passed by
during that time.
I think the killer moved the body
through this gap.
Here too?
This is also a door.
A DOOR ON THE OTHER SIDE?
THE DOOR LEADS TO THE EMPTY LOT
You can get to the empty lot through here.
- There are two secret passageways.
- What?
You can reach the empty lot
through this door.
Gun-mi knew about this secret passageway.
She told me about the door
that led to Sensibility Bar.
I came in through that door
- to beat up Lee Eighty.
- You did?
However, I didn't know
there was a door leading out here.
- Okay.
- I knew about this passageway too.
- How so?
- Gun-mi was my friend.
We would slip out
through the secret passageway
when we drank past nine o'clock
and the cops showed up.
The killer could've come through that door
and dumped the body here.
Let's see if the sign
fits through this door.
Does it fit?
Just barely.
Hey, it fits.
This can't be done.
- Why? Does it not fit?
- It doesn't fit.
THE SIGN WON'T FIT THROUGH THE DOORWAY
This is confusing.
This is so confusing.
So, you can get in, but you can't get out.
That means
the secret passageway wasn't used.
The only person who knew
that the truck would block the CCTV
was C-store.
If that's the case...
It could've been done another way.
Shouldn't we check
when the roads were blocked?
I can tell you that.
The road was open
from 10:30 p.m. to 11:15 p.m.
It was open for 45 minutes.
The killer likely moved the body down here
when the road was open.
Hold on.
Do you also see that nail?
Yeah, I see it.
- What's with that nail?
- Hold on.
Is it stuck, or is it just in the water?
- Is it stuck in there?
- It is.
There's a nail over there.
Could it have come from the sign?
- Check if it's missing a nail.
- That seems unlikely.
What is it?
- There might be a scratch mark.
- Doesn't this look scratched?
Or maybe not.
This is a scratch mark.
Isn't this scratch caused by that nail?
This must be
where the killer passed through.
- The back door.
- Through here?
WAS IT SCRATCHED BY A NAIL
WHILE PASSING THROUGH?
What if Gun-mi was killed
while the roadblock was lifted
and her body was moved through here?
- Between 10:30 p.m. and 11:15 p.m.?
- That's from 10:30 p.m. to 11:15 p.m.
Detective, let's consider this
our time frame and weigh our options.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
COMBINE THE CLUES
TO COMPLETE THE DEDUCTION
This is your last chance
to show us anything you're carrying
that we haven't seen yet.
I gave you everything I had.
I never got the chance to tell you
about this earlier.
- After all this time?
- Is he serious?
- It's nothing. I just found this.
- You had plenty of time to tell us.
- Where did you find this?
- Whose is it?
- It's hers!
There's a photo. It's Gun-mi's.
Gun-mi must've had two phones.
One for Gun-jun, and one for Gun-mi.
I wonder why the screen is cracked.
- Why do you have this?
- I--
- Mister, why do you have it?
- What did you do?
This is why I stepped out of the meeting.
The frame in this photo
matched the one in the video.
I went to my office to confirm it.
- That's why I ran into you at 9:50 p.m.
- It was after I discovered the frame.
After checking the video,
I stormed out of my office,
angry that Lee Gun-mi
had been Park Hyeon-jun all along.
And she was there, running past my office.
- At what time?
- At 9:45 p.m.
- At 9:45 p.m.?
- There was a lot of valuable information
- At 9:45 p.m.
- on her phone.
- She was still alive at the time.
Things got physical between us
when I tried to take her phone.
A physical altercation?
That brat shoved me off and ran,
but dropped her phone.
- I picked it up since I needed it.
- As in this phone?
Which direction did she run off to?
Toward Hansim Pocha.
But what if someone called
while I had this phone?
That's why I turned it off
and put it in my pocket.
After 9:45 p.m.,
we don't know where Gun-mi went
after running off in this direction.
The main point we need to focus on
is that Gun-mi died over there.
- Behind the fried chicken restaurant.
- Between that restaurant and the club.
- Between the two places.
- She died in the alley in between.
Meanwhile, the killer could've taken
three possible routes to move her body.
Route A passes through the blocked road
and by the convenience store.
Route B passes Sensibility Bar,
where a CCTV has been installed.
Route C passes directly through
Sensibility Bar to the empty lot.
Those are the three routes.
However, we checked
the routes ourselves earlier.
- It wouldn't fit.
- Route C is too narrow.
Then the route they most likely took
is Route A,
which was blocked off due to flooding.
- That's what I think.
- I agree.
The flood restriction sign
has a scratch that appears
to have been caused by a nail.
The roadblock
was temporarily lifted last night.
- It was lifted at 10:30 p.m.
- From 10:30 p.m. to 11:15 p.m.
While the roadblock was briefly lifted,
the killer moved the body
hidden inside the sign
and dumped it in the empty lot.
And they must've moved the sign back
before the roadblock was reinstalled.
Also,
there was blood on the box
found behind the chicken restaurant.
That wasn't random.
The killer beat the victim to death,
but there was no way
they could move the body just yet.
Not knowing what to do,
they chose to temporarily hide
the body there.
After keeping it there for a bit,
they took the flood restriction sign
when the time seemed right
and moved the body hidden inside it.
That means there's a good chance she died
before the roadblock was lifted.
That's right.
The time of death was most likely
- before the roadblock was lifted.
- It was before, not after.
After killing the victim,
the killer initially hid the body
and moved it afterward
when the time was right.
Two crimes were committed.
What we haven't been
able to figure out yet
is why the killer chose to move the body
all the way over there.
We have to figure out
why the killer moved the body.
Hold on.
We heard a loud crash at 9:15 p.m.
CAUSED BY PARK CHICKEN
She got into a fight with me at 9:15 p.m.
Maybe the killer went out of their way
to move the body to the empty lot
to frame someone.
- The one caught on video was...
- Ms. Chicken.
- It was me.
- Right, it was you.
Someone who knew
about the commotion she caused
used it to their advantage.
So you're saying,
they knew about the altercation
and moved the body to frame Chicken?
- They made her the prime suspect, right?
- Yeah.
Who witnessed the altercation
between Chicken and the victim?
I did.
- An Dancer.
- Who else?
I only heard the sound.
- Where did you hear it?
- From my office.
- I heard it at the convenience store.
- I saw it from the hallway of the office.
- Which office?
- Whose office?
After submitting the registration form
at Gold Spoon's office,
- So, on your way out?
- I heard a crash and looked outside.
- Here's what I find odd though.
- Can't you see it from his office?
I guess I could've seen
what made the noise.
But as you know, I was busy.
- I guess you would've been busy.
- Right.
I wasn't all that curious about the noise.
Couldn't you have also seen it
if you were at the convenience store?
- I only heard it.
- I only heard it as well.
- Why didn't Gold Spoon see it?
- We were together.
- I was busy at the time.
- But Mr. Club left.
Dancer was the only one
who actually saw the altercation.
Right.
Mr. Club could be lying
about not seeing what happened
when he actually did.
- Mr. Club left after getting cigarettes.
- Right.
There's a chance
Mr. Club also saw me leaving the empty lot
while grabbing onto Gun-mi's hair.
They fought in that empty lot
for about five minutes.
I called Gun-mi at 9:20 p.m.
after seeing that Ms. Chicken had left.
Having ruled out Ms. Chicken as a suspect,
I turned my attention to the others.
I was the only one
who witnessed their fight,
which means one of them must be lying.
In this case, it boils down to
who can provide a valid alibi.
I say this because
the primary location is Hansim Pocha.
So, on the day of the murder,
this meeting was the main event.
Even Dancer was present,
not as an employee of the club,
but as a proxy
for the owner of Sensibility Bar.
Except for Ms. Chicken,
everyone else had to attend the meeting
for various reasons.
The estimated time frame of the murder
is between 9:45 p.m. and 11:15 p.m.
There's no way the killer spent
the entire hour and a half
killing and cleaning up.
They must've gone back and forth.
Hold on.
Dancer, you kept texting the victim
but didn't get a reply.
- Right.
- At least for a while.
What was the text you eventually received?
After seeing her altercation with Chicken,
I called to ask if she was all right.
She said she couldn't get the money
because of her
and postponed our meet-up time
to 9:50 p.m.
But after that,
I lost contact with her again.
- And her phone was turned off.
- Where were you going to meet?
Outside Club Slam.
When did you return to the meeting?
I left at 9:50 p.m. and waited,
but she didn't show up.
I tried calling her a minute later,
but her phone was off.
- So, Club Slam, 9:51 p.m.
- Gun-mi's phone.
- At what time?
- That's when he turned it off.
I turned it off around that time.
- That's when Gold Spoon turned it off.
-"Phone was turned off."
- And then what?
- I went to Gun-mi's place at 9:55 p.m.
That's when I saw
her plane ticket to Russia.
Then I left.
We voted at 10:00 p.m., remember?
Finding Gun-mi was important,
but the vote was just as important.
On my way back to Hansim Pocha,
I got a call from my Mr. Club.
He told me the water leak detector
went off again and to go check on it.
So, I arrived at the club
at around 10:10 p.m.
and came back to Hansim Pocha
at 10:20 p.m.
She came back.
We all cast our vote at 10:30 p.m.,
and Mr. Club sent me out again
at 10:40 p.m.
I was told to check things at the club.
Did you stay at the club?
- She was here at 10:40 p.m.
- No, I came back here at 11 p.m.
That's when I found the flash drive
and checked what was on it.
Why were you wandering around so much?
- She got back at 11:00 p.m.?
- On my way to the club from here,
I found a flash drive identical
to the one I'd given her.
After dealing with the detector,
I went to the break room
to check the flash drive.
Did you find it out there on the street?
Yes, on my way to the club.
Did you say
the water leak detector went off twice?
Yes.
When it first went off,
I planned to send her to the club
during the meeting, but she wasn't around.
So I had no choice but to go there myself.
That was at 9:55 p.m.
- That was 9:55 p.m.
- And then what?
That's also when I got a text
from Gu Lackey.
He looked for what I had asked,
but didn't find anything.
When I looked at the photo again,
something was off.
So at 10:05 p.m.,
I told Lackey to look for missing boys.
Once I got to the club,
I saw that the detector had malfunctioned.
- And then--
- Was it a malfunction?
It kept going off,
even though there was no water leak.
But I couldn't be bothered,
so I told Dancer to deal with it
and returned to the meeting.
I got back here at 10:25 p.m.
- What took you so long?
- At 10:25 p.m.?
But the water leak detector
went off again.
That was around 10:40 p.m.
- Dancer was at the meeting then.
- Right.
So I told her to go check on it.
- Was it another malfunction?
- Yeah.
- Another one?
At 10:50 p.m., Lackey called
to tell me about the missing boy.
That's when I went to Gun-mi's place
to confront her.
- But no one was home.
- Right.
Having had no luck,
I walked past the police station
and returned to Hansim Pocha at 11:15 p.m.
There's something I'd like to ask.
At 10:20 p.m., you texted Lackey
to call you as soon as he had something.
- I did.
- When did he call?
- At 10:50 p.m.
- Could Club have killed her at 10:50 p.m.?
- By that time, you knew the whole truth.
Including the fact that Gun-mi was
going to commit arson to get her revenge.
I had no idea about the whole arson thing.
I was just anxious
about the whole situation.
So my priority was to meet her
and hear her side of the story.
And if anything,
she would've been the one trying to
kill me, not the other way around.
That was her plan.
- Right?
- Maybe that's why you beat her to it.
To protect himself?
That's ridiculous.
I had absolutely no idea
that she had gasoline
and was thinking about killing me
by setting me on fire.
But you would've known
if you saw the gasoline at her house.
I didn't see it though.
What if you became sure of it
at 10:50 p.m.?
- Be sure of what?
- That she was actually Park Hyeon-jun.
He could've known for sure
when Lackey texted him.
- And he could've seen the gasoline
- I bet he knew for sure.
when he went to Gun-mi's house.
Mr. Club could've been the killer.
The roadblock was lifted,
so he could've killed her,
disposed of the body,
and returned by 11:15 p.m.
Come on.
All right, let's say all of that is true.
Kim Club and An Dancer.
They wandered around a lot that night.
An Dancer left the meeting
twice that night,
and Kim Club did the same.
They both had enough time
to commit the crime.
What about you, C-store?
JANG C-STORE'S MOVEMENTS
I arrived at the meeting at 10:10 p.m.,
but before that,
I had been looking for Gun-jun.
I stayed at the meeting
and left without casting my vote.
What time did you leave?
At 11:00 p.m.
Why didn't you sign out
before leaving at 11:00 p.m.?
Because it was raining.
- You just didn't feel like it?
- I was looking for someone.
Were you out doing the thing
that brought you inner peace?
Yeah.
I just love them.
- Love what?
- Petite women with long hair.
- Especially on rainy days.
- Yeah, on rainy days.
He attacks women
- with a claw hammer on rainy days.
- Why does he act so proud of it?
It's okay. He'll be behind bars soon.
JANG C-STORE IS BOUND TO
END UP IN JAIL ANYWAY
Moving on.
- Let's check Mr. Gold Spoon's whereabouts.
- Sure.
- My whereabouts are clear.
- Okay.
- I left the meeting at 10:15 p.m.
- At 10:15 p.m.?
I wasn't in the best of moods
because all I had was Gun-mi's phone
and no idea where she was.
Anyway, I left the meeting
only to find that this road was blocked.
I walked past Sensibility Bar
and went to Lee Gun-mi's place.
That was when the truck
was parked outside the bar.
I didn't notice it
because it's not unusual
to see a truck there.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
I went to Gun-mi's place
and saw what everyone here saw,
which was her suitcase
and plane ticket to Russia.
There wasn't much I could do,
so I came back to the meeting
at 10:35 p.m.
When did you leave again
after coming back to Hansim Pocha?
I returned to my office at midnight.
- You stayed until midnight?
- I was at the meeting all night.
I gave legal advice
to some of the business owners.
- Here?
- Yes.
So, you left the meeting just once
within the time frame of the murder.
That's right.
When we compare his statements
to the theory we came up with,
- his movements don't add up.
- He's no longer a suspect.
He couldn't have gone through that road
at the time the roadblock was lifted.
Based on the timeline we've established,
these three are the prime suspects.
During this time frame...
We're the only ones
who left the meeting twice.
There's one thing that keeps bugging me.
The water leak detector malfunctioned,
and it happened twice.
As a result,
their movements appear very suspicious.
The point I want to emphasize
about the detector
is that I had no say over it.
I don't get the notification
since I'm not the boss.
What I don't get is why he kept
telling me to handle it.
- Who else would I ask then?
- The water leak detector
may sound like a complex device,
but all we do to fix it
is change the batteries.
Besides, it frequently malfunctions
during humid, rainy days in the summer.
- You could've easily handled it.
- Why should I?
Why would you bother
your employee like that?
Who else would I boss around then?
- You were already there.
- Why else would I pay you?
- Look, mister.
- You could've fixed it yourself. Yes?
- Hey, mister.
- Oh, him.
You went to the club
and saw the detector malfunctioning,
but left it to Dancer to fix it
instead of doing it yourself, right?
It's just a nuisance,
especially with this big belly of mine.
It's such a hassle to pick it up
and fiddle with it.
- Maybe there was a reason
- I can barely see those tiny batteries.
- to leave at 10:05 p.m.
- That's so suspicious.
You don't know how tough running
a business is until you've done it. Jeez.
I suppose that's understandable,
but he was there at the club.
He took the time to go there, after all.
But if he was busy with something else,
he could've had Dancer
take care of the detector instead.
I'm wondering if he sent me there
to keep me in one place.
I only went to check on it
because Mr. Club told me to.
- Right.
- That's what I'm wondering.
- Okay, I get it now.
- Hold on.
I never thought that having my employees
handle minor tasks
would come across as suspicious or wrong.
However,
she knows I always tell her
to take care of such tasks.
The water leak detector keeps going off,
and she knows that.
She knew I'd send her to fix it.
- What?
- Get it?
So what though?
She can't just magically
make it malfunction remotely, can she?
You saw it yourselves at the club.
I never touch it myself.
I just notice that there's something
wrong with it and tell her to fix it.
She probably knows how to work it and all.
She could've caused
the detector to malfunction
so that I'd receive a notification.
It's a thought that just occurred to me.
Wouldn't she have to be at the club
to pull that off?
Who knows?
I don't know anything about that device.
It never crossed my mind until now,
but she was wandering outside all night.
But she was here at the time
you sent her to fix it again.
- Is that so?
- I was here at 10:20 p.m.
Then I guess
she could've set it on a timer
or something.
I don't deal with this kind of stuff.
I'm the boss, damn it!
- I mean, if you ever--
- Are you kidding me? Hey!
- For goodness' sake.
- Man, you people are really testing me!
You can't just shout us down, Mr. Club.
So much for trying to control my temper.
You brat!
What?
Here's the thing about Mr. Club.
Let me tell you something about him.
He wasn't in a good mood
when he came to buy cigarettes.
How could I be?
How could I be in a good mood
knowing that the kid of the family
whose house I set on fire 20 years ago
and thought I had killed was still alive?
- All right, then.
- Got it, Mr. Club.
Shush, you punk!
- I'm sorry.
- At 10:20 p.m.,
- I got in touch with Gu Lackey.
- Let's send him to jail.
That was it!
- This is tough.
- Where are you going?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- I wasn't done talking!
Kim Club.
Why did he keep sending me to the club?
She's out to make me the culprit.
Trying to be smart, are you?
That brat!
CAST YOUR VOTE BASED ON THE CLUES
No matter how much I think about it...
Let's say the detector went off.
PLAYING OUT THE SCENARIO
INVOLVING THE WATER LEAK DETECTOR
"Damn, it went off again."
You come in...
and pick up the detector to fix it.
How's that a hassle?
He got Dancer to leave twice
because of this.
It's a piece of cake.
Fixing it himself would've been quicker
than calling Dancer over.
He could've just fixed the detector
since he was there,
but he had me come instead.
Regarding that,
Mr. Club received the notification
about the water leak detector
at 9:55 p.m.,
and initially went to the club.
Then, he called me at 10:05 p.m.
and told me to fix the detector,
and he returned to Hansim Pocha
at 10:25 p.m.
That means there was
a 20-minute gap in between.
He took longer than I did
to get back to Hansim Pocha.
What if he didn't go to the club
from Hansim Pocha?
He killed an entire family.
And after so many years,
he was faced with the possibility
of someone seeking revenge.
He must've been terrified and anxious.
What if he met Gun-mi
during those 20 minutes?
He could've made up his mind to kill her.
He must've been terrified.
Fear drives people
to take drastic measures.
You're the culprit.
All right, Kim Club.
Mr. Club.
I'm sorry.
JANG C-STORE AND AN DANCER CHOSE KIM CLUB
An Dancer had no say in it.
She had to follow Kim Club's order.
That's why I saw her as someone
with limited free will.
Could this have been used?
This means An Dancer
is a likely suspect too.
This is above it.
There are people
who left the meeting twice that night.
One of them is An Dancer.
Kim Club also left the meeting
a second time.
The culprit had to return to the meeting
to create an alibi,
then leave again to move the body.
What would they do?
They needed a reason to leave the meeting
without raising suspicion.
And what reason did they come up with?
The water leak detector.
It drops directly onto it.
The water leak detector
was located directly below
where the hand sanitizer would drip.
They came up with a trick
to intentionally trigger the detector
with a time delay.
After killing the victim,
the culprit stashed the body
in the nearby recycling station
and thought things over.
She knew her damn boss would order her
to fix the water leak detector.
Knowing that,
she was sure
she would be sent out to fix it
if it went off during the meeting.
While pretending
to go out to fix the detector,
she could've taken that opportunity
to move the body to the empty lot.
You played it smart.
I'm impressed, An Dancer.
You...
deserve to rot in jail.
KIM CLUB CHOSE AN DANCER
You were given
a beautiful new face
and deserved to debut.
The betrayal must've cut deep.
Regardless,
you need to be punished for what you did.
JANG DETECTIVE CHOSE AN DANCER
Can I really base my entire deduction
on that one vague piece of evidence
I found in the final three minutes
concerning the leak detector?
Even so...
WHO DID HA GOLD SPOON CHOOSE?
Kim Club and An Dancer.
Given the timeline,
either of them could've done it.
From that moment,
I realized it all came down
to their movements and alibis.
Let's see.
If An Dancer was the one
who moved the body,
she likely killed the victim
when she first left the meeting.
But there's proof
that she called Lee Gun-mi at 10:55 p.m.
Think about it.
Why would she call a dead person?
Does it mean An Dancer isn't the killer?
Did she call to check if she was alive
because she believed she wasn't dead?
FINAL VOTE COMPLETE
The fourth episode of the deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
The results of the nail-biting
deduction game to find the culprit
of the murder in the nightlife district.
Let's see who received the most votes
as the real culprit.
We will now announce the results.
- You didn't vote for me, did you?
- Come on.
Mr. Club, did you vote for me?
The ultimate deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
First, we will announce who was excluded
from the final list of suspects.
The results of the final vote
to determine the culprit are as follows.
With zero votes,
Park Chicken
and Ha Gold Spoon,
you are excluded from the final lineup.
There's an unexpected someone in the mix.
Seriously?
Detective.
Next.
With one vote,
Jang C-store, you are also excluded
from the final lineup.
Why am I in the final lineup again?
- Those identified as suspects
- Who voted for me?
were An Dancer and Kim Club.
Will the two final suspects
please step forward?
You've got to be kidding me.
I can't believe I'm being accused
alongside this thug.
Mind your manners.
Why should I?
The ultimate deduction game,
- Crime Scene Zero.
- What if they're tied?
The results of the final vote
of the murder in the nightlife district.
The player who was ultimately identified
as the culprit is...
An Dancer
and Kim Club!
As it's a three-to-three tie...
An Dancer
and Kim Club!
As it's a three-to-three tie,
the players will decide
by reaching an agreement.
- A three-to-three tie?
- Who was it?
- Which three chose me?
- It's a three-to-three tie.
- They chose each other.
Those who voted for An Dancer
are Jang Detective,
Park Chicken, and Kim Club.
Those who voted for Kim Club
are An Dancer,
Ha Gold Spoon, and Jang C-store.
You must now reach an agreement
and identify the final suspect.
We have to reach an agreement?
Mr. Club, go stand over there.
It suits you better.
What are you talking about?
You go over there.
- Have you ever danced in a cage before?
- Go already.
Since they're our final suspects,
we'll hear their closing arguments.
- Mr. Club, you go first.
- Sure.
Like I said before,
all I did was order my employee
to check on the water leak detector.
Knowing I'd order her to do it,
she took advantage of the situation.
She knew I'd send her to the club
when I got the notification
about a water leak.
- She moved the body in that window.
- That's an important point.
Besides, how could I have known
if the road was flooded or not?
How could I have known
to move the body through there?
- The same goes for Dancer.
- She wouldn't have known either.
I'm the boss, damn it!
You idiots are unbelievable.
It wasn't me!
- His final words were of no use.
- I'm the boss!
- All he did was yell.
- I know.
- All he did was show his nasty temper.
- All right.
I'd like to point out two things.
First,
I believe Mr. Club kept me at the club
by sending me there to fix the detector.
If not for that,
I would've kept looking for him.
While I was at the club,
he used that time to kill the victim
and dispose of her body.
The second thing is something
I want you to think about.
Mr. Club said he heard the crash
but didn't see anything.
- That was at 9:15 p.m.
- Right.
But at that time,
that road was blocked due to flooding.
The quickest way back to the club
was the route past the empty lot.
So, what reason did he have
for taking the longer way back
past the police station?
Here's why I'm bringing that up.
We've established that the body was moved
to the empty lot to frame Ms. Chicken.
Whether the culprit knows
about her altercation with Gun-mi
- is a crucial point.
- True.
- But he chose to lie about it--
- You admitted to seeing it.
I did, but why would I admit it
if I were the culprit?
- Okay, we'll gather our opinions now.
- I didn't see it.
- An Dancer.
- Mr. Club.
- I've been so good to you.
- How do you figure that?
I even made a fair deal
on your labor contract.
They both had plenty of time
to kill and dispose of the body.
But there's more to consider than that.
There needs to be a clear motive
and strong evidence.
They both had enough time to kill her.
But within that window of opportunity,
did the culprit have a clear reason
to kill her?
An Dancer said she left at 9:50 p.m.
- and went to Gun-mi's place at 9:55 p.m.
- Right.
While she was there,
she saw the plane ticket on her laptop.
But at that point, Mr. Club
still didn't have a motive to kill her
because he received the call
from Gu Lackey about the missing boy
at 10:50 p.m.
At the time he first left the meeting,
- he didn't have a motive to kill her.
- You're absolutely right.
But to argue against this,
An Dancer could bring up
the outgoing call he made to Gu Lackey.
- What?
- He called Gu Lackey earlier that night.
One could also argue that Kim Club
heard about who Lee Gun-mi was
before the time
he claimed to have heard it.
I originally thought it was Kim Club,
but then I switched to Dancer.
Let's do this.
We've discussed it, but ultimately,
it's up to you who you vote for.
Vote wisely.
Now,
please identify the final suspect.
Oh, we line up behind the person?
You've got to be kidding me.
(EMPTY)
An Dancer, you've been identified
- It's rather empty here.
- as the final suspect.
Please enter the jail.
You people are unbelievable.
I did find you suspicious
until the end though.
- Mr. Attorney.
- Very suspicious.
She's pissed.
- Someone else could die.
- I'm too scared to make eye contact.
If An Dancer is the real culprit,
Park Chicken, Kim Club,
Ha Gold Spoon, and Jang C-store
will each win two million won,
and Jang Detective will win a million won.
Darn, the detective doesn't get much.
If An Dancer is not the culprit,
the real killer will claim the prize money
of all other players,
a total of ten million won.
The stakes are high.
The fourth episode of the ultimate
deduction game, Crime Scene Zero.
An Dancer has been voted as the culprit
in the murder in the nightlife district.
Is she really the culprit
who killed Lee Gun-jun?
We could all be wrong.
What's with that evil laugh?
Ms. An Dancer.
Are you
Lee Gun-jun's killer?
Yes, she is!
SUCCESSFULLY APPREHENDED THE CULPRIT
See that, people? I never lied.
Good job.
- Those final three minutes mattered.
- Nicely done.
- What a shame.
- She convinced us all.
- That was close.
- Thanks for trusting me.
- I have goosebumps.
- Why did you suddenly change your mind?
- I changed my mind at the last second.
- I was on the fence,
so I trusted my initial gut
but changed my mind just a minute ago.
You confused us
because all you did was claim
that you gave orders
because you were her boss.
- You people brought back my nasty temper!
- You dug your own grave.
We'll now announce
the key piece of evidence you missed.
- Bring it!
- Did we miss something?
Is it alcohol or drugs?
- Is that soju?
- What could it have been?
I told you something was up
with the water leak detector.
- Wasn't it the hand sanitizer?
- Did she cause a reaction with alcohol?
- Guess how I did it.
- She made a hole in the cap.
Like this.
She pierced a hole in the cap
and hung the bottle above it.
- She hung it?
- The soju dripped from the bottle.
Oh, she did that with soju?
She hung it in the sanitizer holder?
THE SOJU BOTTLE WAS HUNG
IN THE HAND SANITIZER HOLDER
The first detector alert was a test,
but the second one
was intentionally triggered.
SHE TRICKED THE DEVICE INTO
SENDING A NOTIFICATION TO KIM CLUB
Where was this?
It was at the club.
A CRATE OF SOJU BOTTLES
WAS BY THE CLUB ENTRANCE
The pin was also on the floor.
- It was?
- Anyway, the water leak detector
- turned out to be a major clue for us.
- Yeah.
Wait, then Gun-jun... I can't believe him.
- You're quite strong.
- You're brutal.
How could you beat someone up like that?
- Should I demonstrate?
- No, we're good.
- I'd be happy to.
- That's not necessary.
THE FULL STORY BEHIND
THE MURDER IN THE NIGHTLIFE DISTRICT
An Dancer had always wanted to be
a K-pop idol since she was young,
but she was turned down
every time she auditioned.
Eventually, she joined
an entertainment agency as a trainee
and was finally close
to making her dream debut
after undergoing a full makeover
with the agency's support.
Then came the words
that completely shattered her world.
To debut,
she would have to repay the money
the agency had spent on her.
As An Dancer despaired over
having no way to repay the money,
the agency suggested she deliver drugs.
After learning that all the other trainees
had paid off their debts
and debuted the same way,
she started delivering drugs
but was soon caught by the police.
However, instead of a police station,
she was taken to a club
in Gangdam Station's nightlife district.
As it turned out, the agency was a front
for a drug distribution ring
that manipulated trainees
into working as couriers,
and Kim Club, a former cop,
was their leader.
Kim Club made An Dancer
sign an unfair contract
by adding a prison waiver fee
to the initial debt,
which left her no choice
but to work as a dancer at Club Slam
and deliver drugs to private VIP parties.
Then one day,
a woman her age named Lee Gun-mi
approached her,
claiming to be her number one fan.
As their friendship grew quickly,
An Dancer confided in her
about her enormous debts
and her one-sided feelings
for Ha Gold Spoon.
It was then that Lee Gun-mi proposed
a dangerous deal.
She had the chance to make a lot of money
by selling photos of VIP drug parties
to an organization operating in China.
She grew hopeful
that she could pay off her debts
and become free so that
she could finally debut as an idol.
However, a few days later,
she happened to see Lee Gun-mi
and Ha Gold Spoon
being affectionate with each other.
Thinking that her best friend
had betrayed her and stolen her man,
she was overwhelmed with anger.
That night,
she angrily called Lee Gun-mi
to call off the whole deal.
What she heard in response
was the shocking truth.
She told An Dancer
that she was a transgender woman
who hadn't been able to afford surgery
and that her relationship
with Ha Gold Spoon was a misunderstanding.
She explained
that after selling the photos,
they would go to China together,
where she could have
her gender-affirming surgery,
and An Dancer would debut as an idol
with a well-known
entertainment agency in China,
which she had already scouted out for her.
After clearing up the misunderstanding,
An Dancer photographed the VIP drug party
to secure their future.
While giving Lee Gun-mi the photos,
the two promised
they would flee to China together
after An Dancer cleared her debts.
However, at 9:30 p.m.
on the day they agreed to meet,
Lee Gun-mi was unreachable.
Meanwhile, as per Kim Club's order,
Dancer visited Ha Gold Spoon's office
to submit the application
for the meeting of business owners
affected by COVID-19.
A loud crash rang out
as she stepped out of the office.
From the hallway window,
she saw an argument unfolding
in the empty lot.
Consumed by rage,
Park Chicken
was threatening Lee Gun-mi's life.
After Park Chicken left,
An Dancer called Lee Gun-mi,
who postponed their meet-up by 30 minutes
due to a setback.
Having no other choice,
she went to the meeting
with business owners affected by COVID-19
with Kim Club.
However, her anxiety increased
because Lee Gun-mi was unreachable again.
At 9:50 p.m.,
the time they agreed to meet,
An Dancer left the meeting venue.
However, instead of going to Club Slam,
which is where they agreed to meet,
she saw Lee Gun-mi
heading into Ha Gold Spoon's office
and followed her inside.
What she discovered after Lee Gun-mi left
shocked her.
Lee Gun-mi had been selling
not only the VIP drug party photos
but also An Dancer's information
to the organization in China.
She planned to keep
the 1.5 billion won for herself
and blame everything on An Dancer
if anything went wrong.
Now livid, An Dancer
removed the flash drive mid-upload
and shut down the computer.
Just then, Lee Gun-mi returned,
snatched the flash drive from An Dancer,
and sprinted off.
She chased Lee Gun-mi
down the dead-end alley between Club Slam
and Gangster Whole Chicken.
The enraged An Dancer
slammed Lee Gun-mi against the wall
and grabbed the flash drive.
When Lee Gun-mi lunged at her,
she shoved her away,
knocking her to the ground,
then began strangling her
with all her might.
Consumed by extreme anger,
An Dancer lost control
and struck Lee Gun-mi's head
multiple times
with the nearby belt stanchion.
When she finally came to her senses,
Lee Gun-mi was already dead.
An Dancer scrambled to find a way
to hide the body,
panicking over the accidental killing.
Her thoughts
immediately went back to the fight
between Park Chicken and Lee Gun-mi.
Just as she decided
to move the body to the empty lot
to frame Park Chicken,
Kim Club called her.
The water leak detector
malfunctioned again, as usual,
and she was ordered to fix it.
After quickly hiding the body
at the chicken restaurant's
recycling station,
she fixed the water leak detector
at the club,
only to realize 20 minutes had passed
since she left the meeting.
To avoid raising suspicion,
she thought it was best to cast her vote
at the meeting first,
then return later to deal with the body.
To come up with a reason
to leave the venue again,
she punctured a small hole
in the soju bottle cap
and hung it upside down
on the hand sanitizer holder,
allowing it to drip and eventually trigger
the water leak detector.
After returning to the meeting
and casting her vote,
the water leak notification
finally came in.
As expected,
Kim Club ordered her to go fix it again,
giving her a reason to leave the venue.
She quickly fixed the water leak detector
at Club Slam,
put the soju bottle and hand sanitizer
back in place,
and went to move Lee Gun-mi's body.
She couldn't pass the police station
next to Hansim Pocha
because an officer
was stationed outside all night.
The alley between Hansim Pocha
and Goldspoon Building
was blocked due to flooding,
and the Sensibility Bar
had a CCTV installed outside.
Just then,
she recalled the secret passageway
she had found out about
while fleeing a police crackdown
at Sensibility Bar.
She left the club and headed to the body,
planning to move the body
through that passageway.
On her way,
she noticed the flood restriction sign
that had been set aside.
The roadblock had been lifted
as the rain had eased,
and the sign had wheels
and enough space inside,
making it ideal for transporting the body.
Using the sign as a makeshift cart,
she quickly loaded
Lee Gun-mi's body onto it
and went through the now-unblocked alley
to reach the empty lot.
After dumping the body,
she searched Lee Gun-mi's body
for her phone
to leave a call record
and create an alibi, but couldn't find it.
All she could do was leave a missed call,
then return to the meeting
after putting the flood restriction sign
back in place.
She then told Kim Club
that it took her a while
to fix the water leak detector.
Hoping the heavy rain
would wash away any evidence,
she dreamed of the perfect crime
with Park Chicken taking the blame.
HEOYOUNG LAND'S 1ST ANNIVERSARY
Today's game is going to be huge.
This is the ultimate betting game,
open only to the chosen few.
This place is for VIPs only.
Bong-cheon!
What the heck is this?
I'm going to kill whoever did it.
Where's the gun?
You want to be thrown into jail?
I'll show you!
Quiet.
Freeze!
- My gosh!
- What was that?
What the heck?
Subtitle translation by: Yenny Kang